# **Norbertas Lapenas**

27 The Meadows, Old Grange Road, Monasterevin, Co Kildare
Mobile 085 114-9751

E-mail nlapenas@gmail.com

https://norbertasl.github.io/

Linkedin.com/in/norbertas-lapenas

https://github.com/NorbertasL

## **Key Characteristics**

Professional, hard working and motivated individual who is very enthusiastic in starting software development work. I have experience of working in a variety of roles including as a construction operative, window and door installer, delicatessen assistant and as an environmental worker.

I have excellent problem solving, technical, customer service, communication, IT, programming, planning and organisational skills. I have undertaken continuous study throughout my working career to ensure my skills and qualifications are relevant. I am versatile and, as shown below, adapt to new roles and challenges easily. I have excellent team working skills with experience of working in fast paced environments.

## **Career Summary**

**2010-2019** A Gilligan Builders, Ballymount Drive, Ballymount, Dublin 12

Role Construction Operative/Installer

This was a full time and part-time role since 2010 and my duties involved working as a general construction operative on a number of house and school construction projects. I was responsible for groundwork, roofing and assisting the on-site tradespeople. I also assisted in the installation of weather glaze doors and windows.

**2017-2018** Brendan McGee Construction, Monasterevin, Co Kildare

**Role** Construction Operative

This was a short term contract and I worked on a variety of construction projects in Dublin and Portlaoise.

**2015-2017** Junction 14 Service Station, Monasterevin, Co Kildare

**Role** Delicatessen Assistant

My role involved working in the deli section where my duties included the preparation and serving of hot and cold dishes, sandwiches, wraps, salads, baked goods and rolls. I was responsible for maintaining all health and safety standards and ensuring that customers were served food promptly.

## **Career Summary Continued**

**2014-2015** Oxigen Environmental, Naas, Co Kildare

Role Environmental Refuse Collector

I worked as part of a team of environmental refuse collectors providing a refuse collection service to customers throughout county Kildare.

#### **Professional Qualifications**

**2019** Full Stack Developer Course – On-line with Code Institute

2019 County Kildare Leader Partnership, Jigginstown, Naas, Co Kildare

**Business Development Course** 

Marketing QQI Level 5

**2016** Java SE 8 Associate Programmer Certificate

### **On-going Development:**

Safe Pass Certification
Manual Handling Certification
HACCP Course

#### IT Skills:

A broad range of Front and Back end development skills including, but not limited to: Java, Python, SQL, Android Development, Gradle, Git, HTML, CCS, JavaScript, REST API.

Always willing to lean new skills to fill in the gaps.

**2004-2010** Moyle Park College, Clondalkin, Dublin Junior and Leaving Certificates completed.

### **Interests**

Passionate about all aspects of technology including web design, database programming and 3D printing.

Relax by taking on electronic projects and have an interest in motorbikes.

Keep fit through Brazilian Jujitsu and running and I cycled around Europe just to say I did it.

Please visit <a href="https://norbertasl.github.io/">https://norbertasl.github.io/</a> for the most up to date information about me and my work. You can also download a soft copy of this CV.

References available on request.